https://www.betagammasigma.org/home/privacy-policy

We use cookies to make interactions with our website and services easy, meaningful and relevant to you. They help us improve our site by better understanding how our sites are used. By continuing to use this site you are giving us your consent to do this. Please review our privacy policy to learn more.
Privacy Policy
OK
AnnouncementsBlogsCommunitiesDiscussionsEventsGlossarySite ContentLibraries
on this day
between these dates
Posted by
AnnouncementsBlogsCommunitiesDiscussionsEventsGlossarySite ContentLibraries
on this day
between these dates
Posted by
Skip to main content (Press Enter).
Sign in
Skip auxiliary navigation (Press Enter).
BGS StoreConnectBGSCMSNewsDonate
Skip main navigation (Press Enter).
Toggle navigation
HomeAbout What is BGS?Mission/HistoryList of ChaptersEstablishing A New ChapterInvitation ProcessWhy Hire BGS Notable BGS MembersFAQsStaffBoard of GovernorsGoverning DocumentsStudent Design ContestSponsors & AdvertisingCareer CentralMember Resources Interact with Members Find a MemberConnectBGSAlumni NetworkMember Badge Describe BGSMember Information Request Member I.D. NumberMembership VerificationGlobal Events CalendarMember Business DirectoryMember Benefits Educational Benefits Internships and Volunteer OpportunitiesGraduate Scholarships & Tuition Discounts LaSalle UniversityUniversity of TulsaIEOpus CollegeWillamette UniversityMiddlebury InstituteUniversity of MissouriRaymond MasonBrandeis UniversityCentrumUniversity of DallasTest PrepApplication Fee & GMAT/GRE Waiver SchoolsProfessional Benefits InsuranceTravelTech Lenovo ComputersGifts and Services United Parcel Service1800 FlowersChurchill Classic Diploma FramesPublicationsProfessional Attire Brooks BrothersJos A BankK & G FashionMen's WearhouseMoore's Clothing for MenProfessional DevelopmentPrograms/Events OverviewGlobal Leadership Summit (GLS) 2019 GLS Pics & VidsAlumni Career Design ProgramMaster Class SeriesEthical Leadership Certification StudentsChaptersBGS Gives Back Junior AchievementFounders WeekBGS Awards Dean of the YearEntrepreneurial Achievement Nomination InstructionsEA RecipientsBusiness Achievement BA RecipientsChapter HonoreeInternational HonoreeChapter Awards Outstanding ChaptersChapter HonoreeChapter Advisor of the YearChapter Honor RollChapter Honor Roll 2015-2016Chapter Honor Roll 2016-2017Chapter Honor Roll 2017-2018Lessons In LeadershipCollegiate Chapters Access CMSChapter Resources Chapter Toolkit Explaining the Benefits and Values of MembershipBest PracticesPromoting Your ChapterCollegiate Chapter Event IdeasSample Letters/ReleasesRecognition & Tapping Ceremony InfoVirtual Recognition CeremonyChapter Advisor CouncilStudent Officer Resources Student Officer ToolkitCollegiate Chapter Honor RollCollegiate Chapter NotesBronze Key StatueChapter Honorees Nomination FormAlumni Network About the Alumni NetworkAlumni Chapters & GroupsJoin the Alumni NetworkStart a GroupAlumni Resources Alumni Event IdeasChapter HandbookPlanning CalendarAlumni TrainingVirtual EngagementAlumni Network Scholarships/Grants Alumni Chapter Scholarship ProgramAlumni Grant ProgramChapter HonoreeAlumni Network Notes
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and are compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). You can download a copy of our GDPR compliance statement.
The policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
This policy is limited to the information Beta Gamma Sigma International Honor Society (BGS, we, us, our) collects via our online properties (www.betagammasigma.org, connect.betagammasigma.org, members.betagammasigma.org).
Our website has links to external sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy of other sites.
For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, the data controller is BGS.
Information we may collect from you
1.1       We may collect and process the following data about you:
1.1.1    Information that you provide by filling in forms on our websites. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use the site, accepting an invitation for induction into BGS and seeking or obtaining services from us. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
1.1.2    If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
1.1.3    We may ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
1.1.4    Details of transactions you carry out through our site and the fulfillment of your orders.
IP addresses and cookies
2.1      We may collect information about your computer, including (where available) your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
2.2      For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us to estimate our audience sized and usage patterns, to store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests, to speed up your searches, and to recognize you when you return to our site.
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites, visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Where we store your personal data
3.1       This site is operated in the United States. The data protection and privacy laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as the laws in your country. If you are located in the European Union, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to and stored on servers at BGS’ hosting provider, Protech Associates, Inc. in the United States. By using our site, participating in any of our services and providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.
3.1.1    IMPORTANT NOTE: What we do with your information, as well as your rights, may be based on the geographic location of your residence. We will be relying on the most recent information we have about you in applying our privacy policies. It is your responsibility to keep the details of your individual record with us up to date so that we can apply our policies appropriately.
3.2       Our website is secure and all passwords are encrypted in our database.
3.3       You are responsible for keeping your password confidential and we ask you not to share your password with anyone.
3.4       Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site, any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, strict procedures and security measures are used to prevent unauthorized access.
Uses made of the information
4.1       We use information held about you in the following ways:
4.1.1     To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
4.1.2     To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
4.1.3     To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
4.1.4     To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service when you choose to do so.
4.1.5     To notify you about changes to our service.
4.2        If you are an existing customer/member, we will only contact you by electronic means (email) or phone with information about goods and services similar to those that were the subject of a previous service to you.
Communications
5.1       You can subscribe (opt-in) to a number of email updates from BGS. You can unsubscribe (opt-out) at any time. 5.2        All the emails you receive from BGS include an "Unsubscribe" link in the footer that will unsubscribe you from ALL BGS email communications.5.3        Alternatively, if you prefer not to unsubscribe from all email communications, you can specifically select the type of email communications you would like to receive by selecting from the various options listed in the Email Preferences tab on your profile page. You can also access this page through the "Email Preferences" link in the footer of all our email communications.5.4       Please be aware that by choosing to stay opted-out of any or all communications you may miss important information we share regarding your membership with BGS and all related benefits.
Disclosure of your information
6.1        We never share your personal information with a third party, including but not limited to requests for confirmation of your membership with BGS, without explicit written consent/request from you the member. Those requests must be submitted by you, the member, to privacy@betagammasigma.org.6.2       We never share your personal details for marketing purposes with any other individuals or organizations without your permission.
6.3       We may disclose your personal information to third parties in circumstances where we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our website terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of BGS, our members, our customers and others.
6.3.1      We may use third-party electronic payment vendors to process credit card data when our customers/members purchase services or products using credit cards.
6.3.2      We make available to our members certain offers from third-party service providers. If you are taking advantage of any of these offers, you should review that organization’s privacy policy and practices. BGS is not responsible for the privacy and security practices of our benefit partners when our members choose to interact with these partners through links from our sites.
Children’s privacy
7.1         Our sites are not directed toward individuals under the age of 16 and we request that individuals under 16 not provide personal data to BGS. If we learn that we have collected personal data from a child under 16, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.
Your rights
8.1         Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our suppliers and/or customers. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do on accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
8.2       You have the right to request that your personal details be erased by BGS. Requests must be made in writing by email to privacy@betagammasigma.org or by mail to:
BGS, Inc.
Attn: Privacy Support
11814 Borman Drive
St. Louis, MO, USA 63146
You may be requested to provide legal proof of your identity to allow us to complete your request.
Access to information
9.1         You can see the personal data we hold about you when you log in to your account. A subject access request can be made in writing to BGS at privacy@betagammasigma.org.
Changes to our privacy policy
10.1        Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to this page.
Contact
11.1       Questions, comments, and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to privacy@betagammasigma.org.
Beta Gamma Sigma and the Key logo are registered trademarks of Beta Gamma Sigma, Inc.
Beta Gamma Sigma, Inc. 11814 Borman Drive St. Louis , MO 63146 Phone: 314.432.5650 Fax: 314.432.7083 bgshonors@betagammasigma.org
Quicklinks
Mission/History
What is BGS?
To advertise with us, please contact Business Development.Copyright © 2019 Beta Gamma Sigma, all rights reserved.Site by eConverse Media
Powered by Higher Logic
